One day in the 1920’s, a young man asked if he could visit a woman at her home. When he arrived at her home, she was wearing a hat on her head. 

Many people today may not understand what this story means. But any American in the 1920’s would understand. The hat said that the girl would like to go out with him. 

In the past, men liked sitting in the girl’s house to talk, to meet her mother, to have something to eat and to listen to her play the piano. However women would like to go on a date, to go out somewhere interesting. 

This new style of dating began to take the place of the old system of visiting in society in the early 20th century. Nowadays, it is very popular around the world